export type Pair = {
  id: number;
  front: string;
  back: string;
};

export const pairs: Pair[] = [
  { id: 1, front: "Dog", back: "Perro" },
  { id: 2, front: "Cat", back: "Gato" },
  { id: 3, front: "House", back: "Casa" },
  { id: 4, front: "Car", back: "Coche" },
  { id: 5, front: "Tree", back: "Árbol" },
  { id: 6, front: "Sun", back: "Sol" },
  { id: 7, front: "Moon", back: "Luna" },
  { id: 8, front: "Star", back: "Estrella" },
  { id: 9, front: "Bird", back: "Pájaro" },
  { id: 10, front: "Fish", back: "Pez" },
  // Añade más pares
];
